A Finding Aid to the LeRoy Neiman Papers, 1938-2005, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Duke University Museum of Art, Durham, North Carolina
Eiteljorg Museum of American Indian and Western Art, Indianapolis, Indiana
Football Hall of Fame, Canton, Ohio
Grunwald Center, University of California, Los Angeles, Los Angeles, California
Armand Hammer Collection, Los Angeles, California
Harding Museum, Chicago, Illinois
Hayward Museum, Hayward, California
Hermitage Museum, Leningrad, USSR
Illinois State Museum, Springfield, Illinois
Indianapolis Museum of Art, Indianapolis, Indiana
Joslyn Museum, Omaha, Nebraska
Memorial Art Gallery, Rochester, New York
Meridian Museum of Art, Meridian, Mississippi
Michigan State University, Kesage Art Center Gallery, East Lansing, Michigan
Minneapolis Institute of Arts, Minneapolis, Minnesota
Minnesota Historical Society
Minnesota Museum of Art, St. Paul, Minnesota
Mobile Art Gallery and Museum, Mobile, Alabama
Museo de Bellas Artes, Caracas, Venezuela
National Museum of Sport in Art, New York, New York
Niagara University, Niagara, New York
Portland Museum of Art, Portland, Maine
Springfield Museum of Art, Springfield, Massachusetts
Tennis Hall of Fame, Newport, Rhode Island
Tucson Museum of Art, Tucson, Arizona
Tweed Museum of Art, University of Minnesota, Duluth, Minnesota
University Art Gallery, Binghamton, New York
University of California at Los Angeles, Los Angeles, California
University of Illinois, Champaign, Illinois
University of Oklahoma, Norman, Oklahoma
University of Oregon, Eugene, Oregon
University of South Florida, Tampa, Florida
University of Texas, Austin, Texas
Utah Museum of Fine Arts, University of Utah, Salt Lake City, Utah
Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tennessee
Wichita State University, Wichita, Kansas
Whitney Museum. New York, New York
Wodham College, Oxford, England
Yuma Fine Arts Association, Yuma, Arizona
Appendix D: A Listing of LeRoy Neiman Serigraph Releases This list corresponds to newspaper and magazine ads in files 3.3: Felicie Inc. - Advertising and 3.3: Knoedler & Co. - Advertising. This is not a complete inventory.
DateSerigraph
Unknown Bar '21' (offset lithograph)
Unknown Delacroix Tiger
Unknown Elephant Family
Unknown Gorilla Family
Unknown Kenya Leopard
Unknown Lion Pride (offset lithograph)
Unknown Lion Couple
Unknown Polar Bears
Unknown Serengeti Leopard
Unknown Zebra Family
Unknown The Plaza Square
Unknown Stock Market (offset lithograph)
Unknown Neiman Montreal '76 (offset lithograph)
Unknown Winter Olympic Skier, Lake Placid 1980
Unknown P.J. Clark's
Unknown Olympic Slalom
Unknown Dublin Bar
Unknown Le Grand Cuisine
Unknown Little Hitter
Unknown Little Fielder
1975 Le Grand Escalier de l'Opera, 1969
1975 Toots Shor Bar
1975 Club House Turn
1975 Black Panther
1976 Sun Serve
1976 Satchmo
1976 High Seas Sailing
1976 Vegas Blackjack
1976 Golf Landscape
1976 Elephant Stampede
1976 Nadia
1976 America's Cup
1977 Marlin!
1977 High Altitude Skiing
1977 Basketball Superstars
1977 Café aux Deux Magots
1977 The Mallet Men
1977 Bengal Tiger
1977 Giraffe Family
1977 Show Jumper
1977 Outrigger Canoe Race
1978 Metropolitan Opera
1978 Moby Dick Portfolio
1978 Bucking Bronc
1978 The Wildcats
1979 Kentucky Derby
1979 Chateau Hunt
1979 Stretch Stampede
1979 Aegean Sailing
1979 American Bald Eagle
1980 Lake Placid, Eighty, 1980
1981 Stenmark
1981 The Race of the Year
1981 Tour de France
1981 Before the Race
1984 Rush Street Bar
1984 Regents Park
1984 Elephant Nocturne
1985 Six Golfers, 1984
1985 Lady Skier
1985 Harry's Wall Street Bar
1986 Nob Hill
1986 Buena Vista Bar
1986 America's Cup, Australia
1987 Great Dane
1987 Giants - Broncos Classic
1987 24 Hours of Le Mans
1987 Bistro Garden
1987 Left Bank Café
1988 Diamond Head, Hawaii
1988 Napoleon at Waterloo
1988 Piazza del Popolo - Rome
1988 Monte Carlo Suite
1988 Harbor at Monaco
1988 Salle Prive - Monte Carlo
1988 Borzoi
1988 In the Pocket
1988 Magic (Johnson)
1988 Clubhouse at Old St. Andrew's
1989 Polo Lounge
1989 Superplay
1989 President's Birthday Party
1989 Chicago Key Club Bar
1990 Secretariat II
1990 Chicago Options
1990 April at Augusta
1990 Gaming Table
1990 The '21' Club
1991 Homage to Ali
1991 Ted Williams
1991 Café Rive Gauche
1991 Cougar
1991 The Bordello
1992 Hunt Rendezvous
1992 Kilimanjaro Bulls
1992 Paddock at Chantilly
1993 The Maulers
1993 Fouquets
Appendix F: A Listing of "Man at His Leisure" Features in Playboy Magazine
Date Subject/Pages
1958 April Painter of the Urban Scene, p. 49-51
1958 December The Pump Room, Ambassadors East, Chicago, p. 60-61
1959 January Le Café Chambord, p. 52-53
1959 June Romanoff's, p. 62-63
1959 December Moore County Hounds (Southern Pines), p. 68-72
1960 February Hialeah Race Course, p. 52-54
1960 June The Colony, p. 74-75
1960 August Forest Hills, p. 76-77
1961 January Squaw Valley, p. 84-87
1961 March Ernie's, p. 94-95
1961 June The S.S. United States, p. 60-61
1961 July Longchamp - Auteuil, p. 82-85
1961 September La Plaza de Toros, p. 109-111
1961 December Maxim's, p. 130-131
1962 January The French Riviera, p. 103-105
1962 March The Grand National Steeplechase, p. 94-95
1962 May The Cambridge-Oxford Boat Race, p. 96-97
1962 August Las Vegas, p. 86-89
1963 May Monte Carlo, p. 122-125
1963 July Air France, p. 102-103
1963 September Sardi's, World Billiard Championship, p. 150-151
1963 December Madison Square Garden, p. 169-171
1964 April Epsom Derby, p. 120-121
1964 August St. Tropez, p. 62-65
1964 October Chantilly, p. 144-147
1964 December The Lido, p. 159-193
1965 March The New York Playboy Club, p.116-117
1965 August The Girallia Yacht Race, p. 110-111
1965 December The Plaza, Manhattan, p. ?
1966 July The Royal Ascot, p. 110-113
1966 September The America's Cup, p. 168-169
1967 January Discotheques, p. 180-181
1967 June Surfing, p. 112-115
1967 November National Horse Show, p. 143-145
1967 Winter VIP Magazine, Assignment London
1968 January Rosati's, Via Venito, p.?
1969 January The Bolshoi Ballet, p. 199-201
1969 June Le Mans, p. 124-125
1969 August Yugoslavia, p. 126-129
1970 January Morocco, p. 203-207
1970 November Can-Am Race, p. 179-181
1971 January Jamaica, p. 191-193
1972 January Sotheby's Auction Room, p. 171-173
1973 January Super Bowl, p. 187-189
1973 July Summer of '72 - The Hamptons, p. 152-157
Playboy Magazine's "Neiman Sketchbook" Features
Date Subject/Pages
1979 December Teofilo Stevenson, p. 221
1980 January Senator Ted Kennedy, p. 137
1980 February Roller Skating, p. 166 -167
1980 March Charles Mingus, p. 179
Appendix E: Exhibitions
Below is a chronological list of Neiman exhibitions. See the index for an alphabetical list of exhibitions (listed by name of venue under the item "exhibitions") and reference to locations of pertinent archive files.
Date Solo Exhibitions
Oct. 9-Nov. 6, 1959 F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago
March 3-31, 1961 F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago
Feb. 9-March 9, 1962 F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago
March 1962 O'Hana Gallery, London
Nov. 27-Dec. 11, 1962 Galerie O. Bosc, Paris
Oct. 8-19, 1963 Hammer Galleries, New York
January-February, 1965 "Vie de France," Astor Tower French Center, Chicago
Nov. 23-Dec. 4, 1965 Hammer Galleries, New York
March 5-25, 1966 Gallery Richelle, St. Louis
1976 "LeRoy Neiman Retrospective 1949-75," Minnesota Museum of Art, St. Paul
Nov. 1967 Frank Sinatra Film Drawings Exhibition, Gallery of Modern Art, New York
Sept. 26-Oct. 7, 1967 Hammer Galleries, New York
Dec. 26-31, 1968 New York Jets Sketches, Hammer Galleries, New York
May 1-June 10, 1969 "LeRoy Neiman: Paintings and Drawings," Choate School, Wallingford, CT
May 1969 "LeRoy Neiman: Impressions of Atlanta," Heath Gallery, Atlanta, GA
Jan. 20-31, 1970 Hammer Galleries, New York
Oct. 19-Nov. 2, 1971 "Recent Graphics and Drawings", The Far Gallery, New York
April-May, 1972 Museo de Bellas Artes, Caracas
Dec. 1972 Circle Gallery, Chicago
Oct. 31-Nov. 11, 1972 Hammer Galleries, New York
Nov. 22, 1972-Jan. 7, 1973 "Sketches of the XXth Olympiad," Solo Exhibition, Indianapolis Museum of Art
Jan.-Feb. 1973 Circle Gallery, Los Angeles
1973 Circle Gallery, Dallas
March 24, 1973 The Hang -Up Gallery Open House
April-May 1973 Circle Gallery, New York
June 2-23, 1973 Brentano's Gallery, New York
Jan. 24-Feb. 5, 1974 "Ali - Frazier," Circle Gallery, New York
Feb. 3-March 17, 1974 Springfield Museum of Art
1974 Windsor Gallery, Los Angeles
April 30-May 11, 1974 Hammer Galleries, New York
June 22-July 6, 1974 Gallery Hawaii, International Market Place, Honolulu
Sept. 1974 Abercrombie & Fitch
1974 Tobu Gallery, Tokyo
Nov. 1974 Gilbert Gallery, San Francisco
Nov. 1974 Windsor Gallery, New York
Feb. 1975 Carol Condit Galleries, White Plains, NY
March 1975 Art Gallery -Studio 53 Ltd., New York
April 1975 "The Wide World of LeRoy Neiman," Windsor Gallery, Los Angeles
June-July 1975 Moby Dick Traveling Exhibition, Peter Foulger Museum, Nantucket
Aug. 1975 Moby Dick Traveling Exhibition, Sag Harbor, Long Island
Sept. 1975 Moby Dick Traveling Exhibition, Pittsfield, MA
July 1975 Waller's Gallery, Tampa, FL
Sept. 1975 Hess's Gallery, Allentown, PA
Nov. 1975 Meredith Long & Co., Houston
Dec. 4-26, 1975 Thomas Ward Galleries, St. Paul
Dec. 4, 1975-Jan. 24, 1976 Minnesota Museum of Art, St. Paul
Dec. 10, 1975-Jan. 10, 1976 Hammer Galleries, New York
Jan. 21-March 10, 1976 Indianapolis Museum of Art, Downtown Gallery at American Fletcher National Bank
Feb.-May 1976 Emerald Art Galleries, Coronado, CA
March 14-28, 1976 Jewish Community Center, Bridgeport, CT
June 1976 M. Knoedler & Co., London
Aug. 1976 Frank Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago
Aug. 28-Sept. 27, 1976 Gallery Hawaii, Hyatt Recency
Sept. 12-Oct. 6, 1976 Niagara Art Center, Niagara Falls
1976 Art Gallery-Studio 53 Ltd., New York
Oct. 1976 Heit Galleries, Phoenix, AZ
Nov. 16-Dec. 4, 1976 "The Olympic Ring," Hammer Galleries, New York
Dec. 12-19, 1976 Fahlnaes Konstsalong, Sweden
March 1977 Gallery 100, Mishawaka, IN
March 1977 Upstairs Gallery, Beverly Hills
March 1977 Galerie Marc, San Francisco
Aug. 31-Sept. 11, 1977 Galerie Renee & Victor, Stockholm, Sweden
Sept. 1977 Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, San Francisco
Sept. 2-23, 1977 Casa Grafica, Helsinki, Finland
Oct.-Nov. 1977 St. Lawrence National Bank, Ogdensburg NY
May 1978 Meredith Long & Co., Houston
June 1978 Merrill Chase Galleries, Chicago
July 1978 The Art Exchange, Creve Coeur, MO
Oct. 12-Nov. 12, 1978 Elayne Galleries, Minneapolis
Dec. 1978 Gallery Mack, Seattle
Jan. 23-Feb. 10, 1979 Hammer Graphics Gallery, New York
April 7-May 1, 1979 The Art Exchange, Creve Coeur, MO
April 28-May 26, 1979 Percival Galleries, Des Moines
May 1979 Brentano's Gallery, New York
Dec. 4, 1979-Jan. 5, 1980 "Horses," Hammer Galleries, New York
Jan.-Feb. 1980 Olympic Benefit Exhibition, Famous -Barr, St. Louis
June 1980 Brentano's Gallery, New York
July 1980 Nicolas Helion, Paris
July 1-19, 1980 Foster Harmon Galleries of American Art, Sarasota, FL
Oct.-Nov. 1980 Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, San Francisco
Dec. 1980 Horizon Gallery, Waikiki
April 28-May 16, 1981 "LeRoy Neiman Drawings: A Retrospective," Hammer Galleries, New York
Summer 1981 Exhibition of Graphic Works 1971-81, Hammer Graphics Gallery, New York
July-Aug. 1981 Foster Harmon Gallery, Sarasota, FL
July-Aug. 1981 Wichita State University, Ulrich Museum of Art
1981 "Drawings by LeRoy Neiman: A Retrospective," Oklahoma Art Center Sheets Gallery
Sept. 1981 State National Bank, Tiara Gallery
Oct. 1981 Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, San Francisco
Nov. 1981 Turnberry Isle Yacht and Racquet Club, Miami
1982 Turnberry Isle Yacht and Racquet Club, Miami
Feb. 1982 Grigsby Galleries One, Scottsdale, AZ
April 1982 Merrill Chase Galleries, Chicago
April 8-24, 1982 Dean Day Gallery
May 1982 Gallery Mack, Seattle
June 1982 Nevada County Arts Council
Summer 1982 Hammer Galleries, New York
Oct. 4-16, 1982 Harrod's Picture Gallery, London
1983 Turnberry Isle Yacht and Racquet Club, Miami
July 1983 Tokyo, (Gallery?)
Sept. 13-Oct. 1, 1983 "LeRoy Neiman: Winners," Hammer Galleries, New York
October-Nov. 1983 Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, San Francisco
Oct. 1983 "LeRoy Neiman: Winners," Upstairs Gallery, Beverly Hills
Dec. 1983 "LeRoy Neiman: Winners," JoAnn Perse Gallery, Little Rock
Dec. 8-24, 1983 Dean Day Gallery
Dec. 2, 1983-Jan. 15, 1984 Hanson Galleries, New Orleans
Jan.-Feb. 1984 Hanson Galleries, Carmel
July 10-Aug. 10, 1984 "The Olympics: Past and Present," Hammer Graphics Gallery, New York
Aug.-Sept. 1984 "The Olympic Spirit," Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, San Francisco
Nov.-Dec. 1984 "LeRoy Neiman Centennial Art Exhibit," Springfield College Babson Library Hastings Gallery, Springfield, MA
Jan. 1985 Superbowl XIX Exhibition, Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, San Francisco
Feb. 1985 Center Art Galleries, Honolulu
March 1985 Lawrence Ross Galleries, Beverly Hills
May 1985 The Toy Store, Hartford, CT
Nov. 1985 "The LeRoy Neiman Collection," Hammer Galleries, New York
Nov.-Dec. 1985 Lawrence Ross Galleries, Beverly Hills
Feb. 1986 Nob Hill Premier and Exhibition, Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, San Francisco
May 1986 The Toy Store, Hartford, CT
June 1986 Peri -Renneth Gallery, Southampton, NY
July 26-Aug. 17, 1986 Hanson Art Galleries, La Jolla, CA
Oct. 1986 Buena Vista Premier and Exhibition, Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, San Francisco
Oct. 1986 Krannert School of Management
Nov. 1986 Lawrence Ross Galleries, Beverly Hills
1987 Upstairs Gallery, Beverly Hills
March 24-April 11, 1987 "LeRoy Neiman in Moscow," Hammer Galleries, New York
April 1987 New York Friars Club
May 1987 Marlborough Galleries, Boston
June 1987 "Neiman's Neimans," Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, San Francisco
Oct. 1987 Hanson Art Galleries, San Francisco
Oct.-Nov. 1987 Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, Beverly Hills
April-May 1988 "Neiman's World" Touring Exhibition, Japan
April-May 1988 In the Pocket Superbowl XXII painting premier, Allyson Louis Gallery, Bethesda, MD
May 1988 "Monte Carlo Chase," Minotaur Galleries, Las Vegas
Sept. 27-Oct. 4, 1988 "Monte Carlo Chase," L'art et l'automobile gallery, New York
1988 Tretyakov Museum, Moscow
Oct. 1988 Merrill Chase Galleries, Chicago
Nov. 19-Dec. 10, 1988 "LeRoy Neiman: Monte Carlo," Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, San Francisco
Jan. 1989 Backstage Gallery, Osaka, Japan
Feb. 1989 Surf Club, New York
April 1989 "Soft Paintings," Hammer Galleries, New York
April 30-May 15, 1989 Polo Lounge Debut, Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, Beverly Hills
May-June 1989 "Select Works by LeRoy Neiman," Midwest Museum of Art, Elkhart, IN
June-July 1989 Steiner & Young Fine Arts Gallery, Atlanta, GA
June 6-Sept. 9, 1989 L'art et l'automobile gallery, New York
Sept. 1989 Hotrod Vintage Car Museum and Dance Club, New York
Aug. 1989 Baja, New York
Sept. 26-Oct. 14, 1989 "A Salute to Central Park," Hammer Galleries, New York
Nov. 1989 Galerie 224, Laguna Beach, CA
May 1989-Feb. 1990 "The Playboy Collection," Dyansen Gallery Traveling Exhibition, New York, Beverly Hills, Atlantic City, San Francisco, Boston, SoHo
April 1990 Exhibition at "The Art Spirit" Event, Butler Institute of American Art
May 1990 Merv Griffin Resorts Casino Hotel, Atlantic City
May 12-31, 1990 Bay Area Baseball Debut, Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, San Francisco
July-Aug. 1990 "LeRoy Neiman: A Series of Sport Serigraphs," Springfield Art Association, Springfield, IL
Aug. 1990 Gallery One of Writer Square, Denver
Sept.-Oct. 1990 Allyson Louis Gallery
Oct. 1990 Bowles/Sorokko Gallery, Beverly Hills
Sept. 1990 Base Art Collection
Jan. 1991 "LeRoy Neiman: Man at his Leisure," Playboy offices, Chicago
May 1991 "The Prints of LeRoy Neiman 1980-1990," Bowles/Sorokko Gallery, Beverly Hills
Oct.-Nov. 1991 "San Francisco," Bowles/Sorokko Gallery, San Francisco
Feb.-March 1992 The Beatles Debut, Dyansen Gallery, Trump Taj Mahal, Atlantic City
Feb. 17-March 13, 1992 University of Charleston Art Gallery
March 14-April 12, 1992 "LeRoy Neiman: Downtown," Bowles/Sorokko Gallery, SoHo, NY
March 15-April 3, 1992 Foster Harmon Galleries of American Art, Sarasota, FL
Oct. 9-24, 1992 "Big Time Golf," Hammer Galleries, New York
Oct. 22-Nov. 30, 1992 "Big Time Golf," Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, Beverly Hills
Oct. 24-Nov. 30, 1992 "Big Time Golf," Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, San Francisco
Nov. 7-Dec. 1, 1992 "Big Time Golf," Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, New York
Oct.-Nov. 1992 "Big Time Golf," Minotaur Galleries, Las Vegas
Nov. 13-Dec. 13, 1992 "Big Time Golf," Merrill Chase Galleries, Chicago
March-April 1993 City by the Bay Debut, Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, San Francisco
April-May 1993 "An Exhibition of Equine Art," Kentucky Derby Museum
Oct. 7-31, 1993 "Un Américain à Paris," Galerie Marcel Bernheim, Paris
Nov. 1993 Minotaur's Forum Gallery, Las Vegas
Dec. 1993 La Galleria d'Arte, Newport Beach, CA
April 1994 Gateway Gallery, Vail, CO
Sept. 1994 "LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris," Hammer Galleries, New York
Sept.-Oct. 1994 "LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris," Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, New York
Oct. 1994 "LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris," Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, Beverly Hills
Oct. 1994 "LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris," Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, San Francisco
Oct. 1994 "LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris," La Galleria d'Arte, Newport Beach, CA
Dec. 1994 "LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris," Merrill Chase Galleries, Chicago and Buffalo Grove
April-June, 1995 "Racing Retrospective," Kentucky Derby Museum
March-April 1995 Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, San Francisco
Jan.-Feb. 1996 "Superbowl XXX," American Fine Art Editions, Scottsdale, AZ
April 1-May 1, 1996 Paterson Museum, Paterson, NJ
July 1996 Trump Plaza, Atlantic City
Sept.-Oct. 1996 "LeRoy Neiman: Portraits of Our Times, 1946 -96" Bowles/Sorokko/Yarger Galleries, Beverly Hills and San Francisco
April-June 1997 "The Art of Sport," Kentucky Derby Museum
April 3-May 2, 1997 "LeRoy Neiman on Safari," Hammer Galleries, New York
April 1997 "LeRoy Neiman on Safari," La Galleria D'Arte, Newport Beach, CA
May 23-June 30, 1997 "The Safari Suite," Centaur Sculpture Galleries, Las Vegas
1997 Hanson Art Galleries Solo Exhibition, New Orleans
Oct. 1998 "Animals: The Wild and the Tame" Solo Exhibition, Bowles Galleries, San Francisco and Beverly Hills
2000 "A Decade of Retrospective Works by LeRoy Neiman," Hanson Gallery, New Orleans, LA
2000 "A Thirty -Year Retrospective" Solo Exhibition, Timothy Yarger Fine Art
2001 "LeRoy Neiman: Works on Paper," National Art Museum of Sport
2001 "LeRoy Neiman: Master Printmaker," Franklin Bowles Galleries, San Francisco
2001 "LeRoy Neiman - A Retrospective Exhibition of Works on Paper," Fairfield Gallery
2002 "LeRoy Neiman: Thirty Years in San Francisco," Franklin Bowles Galleries, San Francisco
2003 "LeRoy Neiman on Safari," Solo Exhibition, The Wildlife Experience, Parker, Colorado
Nov. 7-Dec. 11, 2003 "LeRoy Neiman in Cuba" Solo Exhibition, Pratt Institute, New York
Date Two-Person Exhibitions
Oct. 9-Nov. 6, 1959 F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago
1973 Alexander Calder and LeRoy Neiman, Nassau Gallery, Baldwin, NY
1978 LeRoy Neiman and Robert Addison, Art Institute of Chicago
1981 LeRoy Neiman/Andy Warhol, LAICA, Los Angeles
1988 "The Mustache Show," Salvador Dali and LeRoy Neiman, Tunnel Club, New York
Date Group Exhibitions
1948 Art Institute of Chicago
Aug. 28-Sept. 6, 1948 Minnesota State Fair
1950 Student Exhibition, Art Institute of Chicago
1951 Student Exhibition, Art Institute of Chicago
Oct. 10-Nov. 9, 1952 Local Artists' Exhibition, Minneapolis Institute of Arts
Oct. 14 -Nov. 15, 1953 Local Artists' Exhibition, Minneapolis Institute of Arts
1953 Annual Exhibit, Art Directors Club of Chicago
1953 "Artists of Chicago and Vicinity," Art Institute of Chicago
May 2-30, 1954 Exhibitions of Prints and Drawings by Twin City Artists, Minneapolis Institute of Arts
Aug. 28-Sept. 6, 1954 Minnesota State Fair
Oct. 29-Nov. 12, 1954 Exhibition of Advertising and Editorial Art, Art Directors Club of Chicago
June 2-July 4, 1955 Instructors Exhibition, Art Institute of Chicago
1955 Carnegie International Exhibition, Carnegie Institute of Art, Pittsburgh
Aug. 27-Sept. 5, 1955 Minnesota State Fair
March 8-April 12, 1956 "Artists of Chicago and Vicinity," Art Institute of Chicago
April 22-May 11, 1956 Chicago Area Show, North Shore Art League
1957 Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Oil Paintings, Corcoran Gallery of Art, Washington, DC
Jan. 17-March 3, 1957 "American Painting and Sculpture," Art Institute of Chicago
Feb. 12-26, 1957 Navy Pier Art Show, Chicago
June-July 1957 Chicago Art Institute
Sept. 15, 1957 Deer Path Art League Annual Fine Arts Festival
Oct. 7-27, 1957 Collectors Club Exhibition
1958 Chicago Public Library
Jan. 17-26, 1958 Art:USA:58
1958 Navy Pier Art Show, Chicago
1958 "Brotherhood in Art," Marshall Field & Co. Gallery
July 6-Aug. 16, 1958 Ravinia Festival
Sept. 1958 Chicago Artists, Anna Werbe Gallery, Detroit, MI
Sept. 6-7, 1958 Old Orchard Art Festival, North Shore Art League, Skokie, IL
Dec. 1958 Frank Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago
June 8, 1959 Bal Tabarin Room, Hotel Sherman, Chicago
July 27-Aug. 10, 1959 Paintings and Photographs by Playboy Jazz Artists, Sherman Art Gallery
Sept. 12-13, 1959 Old Orchard Art Festival, North Shore Art League, Skokie, IL
Nov. 1959 Frank Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago
Feb. 1960 Anshe Emet Cinema Arts Festival
March 31-May 28, 1961 "Artists of Chicago and Vicinity," Art Institute of Chicago
Dec. 13, 1962-Jan. 26, 1963 "Mixed Christmas Exhibition," O'Hana Gallery, London
1964 North Mississippi Valley Exhibition
1965 Frank Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago
March-July 1966 Aqueduct Gallery, New York
May 23-Aug. 24, 1969 "TIME Portraits of American Newsmakers," National Portrait Gallery Traveling Exhibition
May 27, 1969 National Art Museum of Sport
Nov. 1969 Frank Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago
1971 "Beyond Illustration: The Art of Playboy," Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago
Spring 1972 Odyssey House Art Gallery
Sept.-Oct. 1973 Illini Union Art Gallery, Illinois
1974 "Group Show of FKH Artists," Hammer Galleries, New York
Dec. 2, 1974-Jan. 4, 1975 Holiday Exhibition, Hammer Galleries, New York
Feb. 10-22, 1975 "Hammer Galleries Graphics," Hammer Galleries, New York
Sept. 2-Nov. 21, 1975 "Drawings USA 75," Minnesota Museum of Art (Traveled Jan. 1976 -Dec. 1977)
May 2-July 4, 1976 "Watercolor U.S.A. National Invitational Exhibition," Springfield Art Museum, Springfield, MO
Aug. 2-7, 1976 Saratoga Gallery, Saratoga Springs, NY
July 3-Sept. 30, 1977 "National Exhibition of Tennis Art," International Tennis Hall of Fame
June-July 1978 "National Exhibition of Tennis Art," International Tennis Hall of Fame
1977 "Ball, Bat, and Glove," Spectrum Fine Art, New York
Sept. 12-16, 1978 Spectrum Fine Art, Royal Orleans Hotel
1979 "Ringside: The Fine Art of Boxing," Spectrum Fine Art, New York
May 4-July 8, 1979 "Panorama of American Art," Midwest Museum of Art, Elkhart, IN
July 15-20, 1979 "Treasures of Island Creek," Louisville, KY
Jan. 2-Feb. 2, 1980 "Grand Opening Group Exhibition," Foster Harmon Galleries of American Art, Sarasota, FL
April 29-Aug. 31, 1980 "That Belmont Look," New -York Historical Society (NYS Museum, Albany, Jan. -March, 1981)
Nov. 1980 "Fall Portfolio of International Artists," Calgary Inn, Alberta, Canada
1982 "When They Were Very Young," Amherst College Student Art Gallery, Amherst, MA
March 1982 Northampton County Area Community College Foundation
March 1983 "Showstoppers: Great Moments of the American Musical," Museum of the City of New York
Sept. 25-Oct. 22, 1983 "Greenwich Workshop Gallery Miniature Show '83," Greenwich Workshop Gallery
June 1984 "Champions: The Olympic Athlete in Art," San Diego Museum of Art
March 1985 "Americana," Whitney Museum, New York
April-Aug. 1985 "Archives of American Yachting and Boating," Mystic Seaport Museum, Mystic, CT
May 1985 "Art," Area Club, New York
Dec. 1985-Jan. 1986 "American Masters of the 1940s, 50s, and 60s," Frank Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago
March 15-June 28, 1987 "The Horse: Man's Noble Companion," The Monmouth Museum, Lincroft, NJ